The volume of the cell is very important for an oocyte and
very small for a spermatozoon.
One could say that the ovum is in dilation; it is completely open,
fully what we call in extension.
It is open, while the sperm is in internal
rotation.
It is dried out, it is mummified.
On the other hand, the concentration of DNA is very important for
the spermatozoon, in DNA.
The mobility, however, of the oocyte.
The spermatozoon is completely stopped.
The number of these...
produced is about 400. This means that primary oocytes
are formed during the fetal period.
In other words, when you were in your mother's womb, you
were already busy
making your own oocytes. The nourishing cells, the follicular cells,
I...
So one is passed on through development and one is given by the
mother, which will provide axes.
This means that it is a pathway for passing on information on a genetic level,
epigenetically, in a transgenerational manner.
The ovaries need to be inside because they need to be warmed,
they need to be hot, while the testicles are...
descended because it has to be a bit cooler.
This is important when women come in with fertility issues.
Sometimes, when you work at the sacrum level, you may feel cold.
This can be a problem.
Here, we will talk about the duodenum, regarding the arteries and what
we call plicae, little fossae.
The folds at the duodenum level that transmit trophic information
via the arterial system, among other things via the ovarian arteries
or testicular arteries,
it will all depend on where fertility needs to be addressed much higher
in the framework of the facial pentagon of the pancreas.